zimeye.net 2019-12-10

# PRIVACY POLICY | ZimEye

This privacy policy sets out how ZimEye uses and protects any information that you provide ZimEye .

ZimEye is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

ZimEye does not collect personal data. This website uses cookies to collect and process anonymized statistical information such as mobile device used, geographical location for monitoring a user’s city or country, websites tracking, but in any case, ZimEye.com does not link any information to personal data relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.

ZimEye may change this policy from time to time according new legislation and practices by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 2018.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * (if you provide it) (ONLY APPLICABLE TO REGISTERED SUBSCRIBERS) contact information being email address.
  * Your name (if you provide it).

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * (ONLY APPLICABLE TO REGISTERED SUBSCRIBERS) we periodically send emails about ZimEye news articles using the email address which you have provided.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

ZimEye also uses cookies to reach out to people who have previously visited our website or watched one of our videos on YouTube. These ads can appear in your search results and other websites across the internet. If you would rather not see these type of advertisements, you can opt-out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page.

In addition, we utilise Google’s Conversion Tracking program. If you found our website through an advertisement on Google, or any of Google’s affiliated websites, Google uses a session cookie (which does not track personally identifying information) to gather information used in making customer search experiences more relevant. This cookie expires in 30 days.

For more information, please see Google’s Privacy Policy (<http://www.google.com/privacy.html>) or click on the Google Site Stats graphic when it appears on our site.

### How to turn off cookies

Most web browsers (e.g. Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer, Safari…) automatically accept cookies however you can usually modify your cookie preferences in your browser settings to decline cookies if you wish to.

For help on specific web browser settings:

[Safari](http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042) and [iPad, iPhone, iPod Touch](http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677)

If you are mainly concerned about third party advertising cookies, you can turn these off by going to [Your Online Choices Site](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/).

You can also visit the trade body representing these advertising platforms for more information: [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

### Other useful links

For more information about cookies visit [All About Cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

If you have any questions or queries regarding cookies at all, feel free to [email us](https://www.zimeye.net/contact).

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at admin_at_zimeye.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Media Origins Ltd, 15 Queen Square, LS2 8AJ …………………

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
